websitecm.com 2012-05-09

# Privacy Policy

WebsiteCM Software Inc. (hereafter called "WebsiteCM") despises spam, junk mail, cold-calls and other unsolicited forms of being contacted as much as you do, and as such holds your personal information in strict confidence.

**Your Agreement**  
WebsiteCM reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time and solely at our discretion. If possible, we will provide advance notice of significant changes. However, it is your responsibility to check this privacy policy regularly. Your continued use of our Websites after we have made changes signifies that you your accept the changes, whether or not you have reviewed them.

**Scope of Privacy Policy**  
This privacy policy applies to your use of any and all of the websites, now, previously and/or to be owned or operated by WebsiteCM, its subsidiaries and/or affiliated companies (collectively referred in these Terms and Policies as the "Websites").

**Rental or Sale of Identifying Information**  
WebsiteCM does not release, rent or sell member-identifying information to third parties.

**When You Browse Our Site–Anonymous**  
When you browse our Websites, WebsiteCM does not collect your personal information. We collect only aggregate data, such as the number of hits per page. We use this aggregate data to generate statistical reports for our marketing purposes.

**When Visitors Subscribe–Limited Personal Information**  
Visitors to our Websites may choose to subscribe to our communications and publications. Your email address will be registered with our database. You have the option to discontinue receiving our emails at any time.

**Our Links to Third-Party Sites**  
We link to external sites as a service to our members and visitors, and these sites are not under our control. We are not responsible for the content, privacy practices or security measures of these linked sites. Nor does the provision of a link constitute our endorsement of the information, products or services contained on the external site.

**Your Comments and Feedback to Us**  
Any comment, feedback or information you voluntarily provide to us will be deemed as non-confidential unless you specifically stipulate that it should be confidential.

**Lawful Disclosure**  
It may be necessary, if required by law or if pertinent to judicial or governmental investigations, to release your personally identifiable information.  

| 

News

Articles

Testimonials

Another big thumbs up for Jon at Websitecm not only is his mod for CDSEO fantastic but he bent over backwards to help us out when we got shafted by our hosting company. This guy is the only guy we will be buying mods from now on. Some of the other people selling mods for X-cart should take a leaf out of his book because some of them really suck on support and professionalism. 

JoBananas.com 

* * *
